Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 6 5583/6
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Connecticut General Life Insurance, 1939-1949 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Notes and Quotes, 1939-1949 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    Author: Connecticut General Life Insurance
    Notes: no.1 (1939)-no.127 (1949). Employee Relations. Bound volume.
- Connecticut General Life Insurance, 1950-1960 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Notes and Quotes, 1950-1960 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.128 (1950)-no.259 (1960). Bound volume.
- Connecticut General Life Insurance, 1961-1970 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Notes and Quotes, 1961-1970 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.260 (1961)-no.378 (1970). Bound volume.
- Connecticut General Life Insurance, 1971-1975 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Notes and Quotes, 1971-1975 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.379 (1971)-no.424 (1975). Bound volume.
- Alexander Hamilton Institute, 1925-1926 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Office Optimism, 1925-1926 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    Author: Alexander Hamilton Institute
- National Founders Association; National Metal Trades Association, 1923-1924 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Open Shop Review, 1923-1924 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    Author: National Founders Association; National Metal Trades Association
    Notes: v.20 (1923)-v.21 (1924). Bound volume.
- National Founders Association; National Metal Trades Association, 1925-1926 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Open Shop Review, 1925-1926 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22 (1925)-v.23 (1926). Bound volume.
- National Founders Association; National Metal Trades Association, 1927-1928 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Open Shop Review, 1927-1928 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.24 (1927)-v.25 (1928). Bound volume.
- Metropolitan Life Insurance, 1929-1934 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Pacific Coaster, 1929-1934 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    Author: Metropolitan Life Insurance
    Notes: v.11:no.2 (1929:July)- v.16 (1934). Bound volume.
- International Brotherhood of Papermakers, 1923-1926 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Paper Makers Journal, 1923-1926 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    Author: International Brotherhood of Papermakers
    Notes: v.22 (1923)-v.25 (1926). Bound volume.
- International Brotherhood of Papermakers, 1927-1930 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Paper Makers Journal, 1927-1930 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.26 (1927)-v.29 (1930). Bound volume.
- International Brotherhood of Papermakers, 1931-1936 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Paper Makers Journal, 1931-1936 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.30 (1931)-v.35 (1936). Bound volume.
- International Brotherhood of Papermakers, 1937-1941 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Paper Makers Journal, 1937-1941 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36 (1937)-v.40 (1941). Bound volume.
- International Brotherhood of Papermakers, 1942-1946 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Paper Makers Journal, 1942-1946 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.41 (1942)-v.45 (1946). Bound volume.
- International Brotherhood of Papermakers, 1947-1948 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Paper Makers Journal, 1947-1948 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.46 (1947)-v.47:no.3 (1948:June). Bound volume.
- International Brotherhood of Papermakers, 1948-1957 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Paper Makers Journal, 1948-1957 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.47:no.4 (1948:Aug.)-v.56 (1957). Bound volume.
- Peoples Gas Light and Coke, 1922-1925 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Peoples Gas Club News, 1922-1925 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    Author: Peoples Gas Light and Coke
    Notes: v.10 (1922)-v.13 (1925). Bound volume.
- Peoples Gas Light and Coke, 1926-1929 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Peoples Gas Club News, 1926-1929 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.14 (1926)-v.17 (1929). Bound volume.
- Peoples Gas Light and Coke, 1930-1933 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Peoples Gas Club News, 1930-1933 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18 (1930)-v.21 (1933). Bound volume.
- Pere Marquette Railway, 1923-1925 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Pere Marquette Magazine, 1923-1925 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.16 (1923)-v.17 (1925). Bound volume.
- Pere Marquette Railway, 1926-1927 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Pere Marquette Magazine, 1926-1927 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18 (1926)-v.18-A (1927). Bound volume.
- Pere Marquette Railway, 1928-1929 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Pere Marquette Magazine, 1928-1929 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19 (1928)-v.20 (1929). Bound volume.
- Deutsch and Shea, 1951-1954 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Personnel Executives Newsletter, 1951-1954 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    Author: Help Wanted Division
    Notes: v.1:no.11 (1951:Sep.)- v.4:no.4 (1954:Feb.). Bound volume.
- National Association of Manufacturers, 1926-1928 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Pocket Bulletin, 1926-1928 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27 (1926/1927)-v.28 (1927/1928). Bound volume.
- Western Electric Breeze Point Works, 1930-1932 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Pointer, 1930-1932 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    Author: Western Electric Breeze Point Works
    Notes: v.2 (1930)- v.4:no.9 (1932:Aug./Sep.). Bound volume.
- New York State Department of Labor, 1945-1946 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: State of New York Department of Labor Annual Summary of Operations, 1945-1946 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    Author: Division of Placement and Unemployment Insurance
- Bar Association, 1931; Publication (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: State of New York Joint Legislative Committee on Unemployment, 1931; Publication (Box 67, Folder 6)
    Author: Bar Association
    Notes: v.2 (1931:Dec. 18-20). Bound volume.
- Bar Association, 1931; Publication (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: State of New York Joint Legislative Committee on Unemployment, 1931; Publication (Box 67, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.3 (1931:Dec. 2-4). Bound volume.
- Bar Association, 1931; Publication (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: State of New York Joint Legislative Committee on Unemployment, 1931; Publication (Box 67, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.4 (1931:Dec. 17-18). Bound volume.
- Railroad Retirement Board, 1965-1966 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Monthly Review of the Railroad Retirement Board, 1965-1966 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.26 (1965)-v.27 (1966). Bound volume.
- Western Electric Breeze Point Works, 1936-1945 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Pointer, 1936-1945 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.5 (1936)- v.14 (1945). Bound volume.
- Western Electric Breeze Point Works, 1946-1952 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Pointer, 1946-1952 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15 (1946)- v.21 (1952). Bound volume.
- Owens-Illinois Glass Company, 1948-1951 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Personnel Newsnotes, 1948-1951 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    Author: Owens-Illinois Glass Company
    Notes: December 1948 - December 1951. Bound volume.
- Owens-Illinois Glass Company, 1952-1954 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Personnel Newsnotes, 1952-1954 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    Notes: January 1952 - December 1954. Bound volume.
- Owens-Illinois Glass Company, 1955-1956 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Personnel Newsnotes, 1955-1956 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    Notes: January 1955 - December 1956. Bound volume.
- Owens-Illinois Glass Company, 1957-1958 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Personnel Newsnotes, 1957-1958 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    Notes: January 1957 - December 1958. Bound volume.
- Owens-Illinois Glass Company, 1959-1960 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Personnel Newsnotes, 1959-1960 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    Notes: January 1959 - December 1960. Bound volume.
- Owens-Illinois Glass Company, 1961-1963 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Personnel Newsnotes, 1961-1963 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    Notes: January 1961 - December 1963. Bound volume.
- Owens-Illinois Glass Company, 1964-1966 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Personnel Newsnotes, 1964-1966 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    Notes: January 1964 - December 1966. Bound volume.
- Owens-Illinois Glass Company, 1967-1969 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Personnel Newsnotes, 1967-1969 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    Notes: January 1967 - April 1969. Bound volume.
- Pacific Northwest Personnel Management Association, 1954-1959 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Personnel Panorama, 1954-1959 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Author: Pacific Northwest Personnel Management Association
    Notes: v.7:no.1 (1954:Jan.)-v.12:no.5 (1959:Nov./Dec.). Bound volume.
- Pacific Northwest Personnel Management Association, 1960-1961 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Personnel Panorama, 1960-1961 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.12:no.6 (1960:Jan./Feb.)-v.14:no.1 (1961:Jan./Feb.). Bound volume.
- National Retail Dry Goods Association, 1950-1953 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Personnel Service, 1950-1953 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    Author: Personnel Group
    Notes: January/February 1950 - November/December 1953. Bound volume.
- National Retail Dry Goods Association, 1954-1956 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Personnel Service, 1954-1956 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    Notes: January/February 1954 - November/December 1956. Bound volume.
- National Retail Dry Goods Association, 1957-1960 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Personnel Service, 1957-1960 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    Notes: January/February 1957 - September/October 1960. Bound volume.
- National Retail Dry Goods Association, 1961-1963 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Personnel Service, 1961-1963 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    Notes: January/February 1961 - July/October 1963. Bound volume.
- Division 4, Railway Employees Dept. AFL, Montreal, Cn., 1924-1925 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Federated Railwayman, 1924-1925 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    Author: Division 4, Railway Employees Dept. AFL, Montreal, Cn.
    Notes: v.1 (1924)-v.2 (1925). Bound volume.
    Language: English;French.
- National Foremen's Institute, 1943-1946 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Foremen's Letter, 1943-1946 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    Notes: November 24, 1943-December 31, 1946. Bound volume.
- National Association of Foremen, 1926-1928 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Foremen's Magazine, 1926-1928 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    Author: National Association of Foremen
    Notes: v.2 (1926)-v.4 (1928). Bound volume.
- National Association of Foremen, 1929-1931 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Foremen's Magazine, 1929; Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.5 (1929). Bound volume.
  - Item 2: The Foreman, 1930-1931 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.6 (1930)-v.7 (1931). Bound under previous title: Foremen's Magazine. Bound volume.
- National Association of Foremen, 1932-1933 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Foreman, 1932-1933 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.8 (1932)- v.9:no.1 (1933:Jan.). Bound volume
- Rochester Gas and Electric Corporation, 1920-1923 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Gas and Electric News, 1920-1923 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    Author: Rochester Gas and Electric Corporation
    Notes: v.8 (1920)-v.10 (1923). Bound volume.
- Rochester Gas and Electric Corporation, 1923-1926 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Gas and Electric News, 1923-1926 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.11 (1923)-v.13 (1926). Bound volume.
- Rochester Gas and Electric Corporation, 1926-1928 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Gas and Electric News, 1926-1928 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14 (1926)-v.15 (1928). Bound volume.
- Rochester Gas and Electric Corporation, 1928-1930 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Gas and Electric News, 1928-1930 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.16 (1928)-v.17 (1930). Bound volume.
- Consolidated Gas Company of New York, 1922-1927 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Gas Logic, 1922-1927 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    Author: Consolidated Gas Company of New York
    Notes: v.31 (1922)-v.41 (1927). Bound volume.
- Consolidated Gas Company of New York, 1927-1934 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Gas Logic, 1927-1934 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.42 (1927)-v.55 (1934). Bound volume.
- Chicago Great Western Railroad Company, 1922-1925 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Great Western Magazine, 1922-1925 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    Author: Chicago Great Western Railroad Company
    Notes: v.1 (1922)-v.3 (1925). Bound volume.
- Chicago Great Western Railroad Company, 1925-1928 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Great Western Magazine, 1925-1928 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4 (1925)-v.6 (1928). Bound volume.
- Chicago Great Western Railroad Company, 1928-1930 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Great Western Magazine, 1928-1930 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7 (1928)-v.8 (1930). Bound volume.
- United Cloth Hat and Cap Makers of North America, 1916-1917 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Cloth Hat, Cap and Millinery Workers' Journal, 1916-1917 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    Author: United Cloth Hat and Cap Makers of North America
    Notes: v.1 (1916)-v.2:no.2 (1917:Feb.). Bound volume.
    Language: English;Yiddish.
  - Item 2: Headgear Worker, 1917; Publication (Box 73, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.3 (1917:Mar.)-v.2:no.12 (1917:Dec.). Bound with previous title: Cloth Hat, Cap and Millinery Workers' Journal. Bound volume.
- United Cloth Hat and Cap Makers of North America, 1918; Publication (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Headgear Worker, 1918; Publication (Box 73, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3 (1918). Bound volume.
- Manufacturers Association of New Jersey, 1946-1954 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Bulletin, 1946-1954 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    Author: Manufacturers Association of New Jersey
    Notes: Series 1:no.1 (1946:Oct. 16)-Series 9:no.16 (1954:Dec. 17). Bound volume.
- Bar Association, 1931; Publication (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: State of New York Joint Legislative Committee on Unemployment, 1931; Publication (Box 73, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.1 (1931:Nov. 5-6). Bound volume.
- Central Hudson System of Gas and Electric Companies, 1924-1927 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Central Hudson Bulletin, 1924-1927 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    Author: Central Hudson System of Gas and Electric Companies
    Notes: v.4 (1924)-v.7 (1927). Bound volume.
- Central Hudson System of Gas and Electric Companies, 1934-1936 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Central Hudson Bulletin, 1934; Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.14:no.1 (1934:Jan./Mar.). Loose issue.
  - Item 2: Central Hudson Bulletin, 1934; Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.14:no.2 (1934:Year-End). Loose issue.
  - Item 3: Central Hudson Bulletin, 1934; Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.14:no.2 (1934:Year-End). Copy 2. Loose issue.
  - Item 4: Central Hudson Bulletin, 1935; Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.1 (1935:Mid Year). Loose issue.
  - Item 5: Central Hudson Bulletin, 1935; Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.2 (1935:Year-End). Loose issue.
  - Item 6: Central Hudson Bulletin, 1936; Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.16:no.1 (1936:Summer). Loose issue.
  - Item 7: Central Hudson Bulletin, 1936; Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.16:no.2 (1936:Year-End). Loose issue.
- Central Hudson System of Gas and Electric Companies, 1937-1940 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Central Hudson Bulletin, 1937; Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.17:no.1 (1937:Summer). Loose issue.
  - Item 2: Central Hudson Bulletin, 1937; Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.17:no.2 (1937:Year-End). Loose issue.
  - Item 3: Central Hudson Bulletin, 1938; Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.1 (1938:Summer). Loose issue.
  - Item 4: Central Hudson Bulletin, 1938-1939 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.2 (1938/1939:Winter). Loose issue.
  - Item 5: Central Hudson Bulletin, 1939; Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.1 (1939:Summer). Loose issue.
  - Item 6: Central Hudson Bulletin, 1939-1940 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.2 (1939/1940:Winter). Loose issue.
  - Item 7: Central Hudson Bulletin, 1939-1940 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.2 (1939/1940:Winter). Copy 2. Loose issue.
- Central Hudson System of Gas and Electric Companies, 1941-1942 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Central Hudson Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 74, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.20:no.1 (1940:Summer). Loose issue.
  - Item 2: Central Hudson Bulletin, 1940-1941 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.20:no.2 (1940/1941:Winter). Loose issue.
  - Item 3: Central Hudson Bulletin, 1940-1941 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.20:no.2 (1940/1941:Winter). Copy 2. Loose issue.
  - Item 4: Central Hudson Bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 74, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.21:no.1 (1941:Summer). Loose issue.
  - Item 5: Central Hudson Bulletin, 1941-1942 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.21:no.2 (1941/1942:Winter). Loose issue.
  - Item 6: Central Hudson Bulletin, 1942; Publication (Box 74, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.22:no.1 (1942:Summer). Loose issue.
- American Rolling Mill Company, 1920; Publication (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Armco Bulletin, 1920; Publication (Box 74, Folder 6)
    Author: American Rolling Mill Company
    Notes: v.7,no.1-3,5-12 (1920). Bound volume.
- American Rolling Mill Company, 1923-1924 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Armco Bulletin, 1923-1924 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.10 (1923)- v.11 (1924). Bound volume.
- American Rolling Mill Company, 1925-1927 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Armco Bulletin, 1925-1927 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.12 (1925)- v.14 (1927). Bound volume.
- American Rolling Mill Company, 1928-1929 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Armco Bulletin, 1928-1929 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.15 (1928)- v.16 (1929). Bound volume.
- American Rolling Mill Company, 1930; Publication (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Armco Bulletin, 1930; Publication (Box 74, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.17:no.1 (1930:Jan.)-v.17:no.5 (1930:May). Bound volume.
- Office of Federal Committee on Apprentice Training, 1935-1942 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Apprentice Training News, 1935-1942 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    Author: Office of Federal Committee on Apprentice Training
    Notes: October, 1935 - November, 1942. bound volume.
- Atlantic Refining Company, 1923-1925 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Atlantic Seal, 1923-1925 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    Author: Atlantic Refining Company
    Notes: v.1 (1923)-v.2 (1925). Bound volume.
- Atlantic Refining Company, 1925-1927 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Atlantic Seal, 1925-1927 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 (1925:Sept.)-v.4:no.8 (1927:Apr.). Bound volume.
- Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1924-1925 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Baltimore and Ohio Magazine, 1924-1925 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    Author: Baltimore and Ohio Railroad
    Notes: v.12 (1924/1925). Bound volume.
- Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1925-1926 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Baltimore and Ohio Magazine, 1925-1926 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.13 (1925/1926). Bound volume.
- Arm-Co Steel Corporation, 1962-1964 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Armco Operator, 1962-1964 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    Author: Arm-Co Steel Corporation
- Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1926-1927 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Baltimore and Ohio Magazine, 1926-1927 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14 (1926/1927). Bound volume.
- Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1927-1928 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Baltimore and Ohio Magazine, 1927-1928 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15 (1927/1928). Bound volume.
- Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1928-1929 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Baltimore and Ohio Magazine, 1928-1929 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16 (1928/1929). Bound volume.
- Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1929-1930 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Baltimore and Ohio Magazine, 1929-1930 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17 (1929/1930). Bound volume.
- Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1930-1931 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Baltimore and Ohio Magazine, 1930-1931 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18 (1930/1931). Bound volume.
- Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1931-1934 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Baltimore and Ohio Magazine, 1931-1934 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19 (1931/1932)-v.20 (1932/1934). Not published from June 1932 through Apirl 1934. Bound volume.
- Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1935-1936 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Baltimore and Ohio Magazine, 1935-1936 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.21 (1935)-v.22 (1936). Bound volume.
- Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1937-1938 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Baltimore and Ohio Magazine, 1937-1938 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23 (1937)-v.24 (1938). Bound volume.
- Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1939-1940 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Baltimore and Ohio Magazine, 1939-1940 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.25 (1939)-v.26 (1940). Bound volume.
- Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1941-1942 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Baltimore and Ohio Magazine, 1941-1942 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.27 (1941)-v.28 (1942). Bound volume.
- Railway Express Agency, 1924-1928 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Express Messenger, 1924-1928 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    Author: Railway Express Agency
    Notes: v.7 (1924/1925)- v.10 (1927/1928). Bound volume.
- Railway Express Agency, 1928-1932 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Express Messenger, 1928-1932 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.11 (1928/1929)-v.14 (1931/1932). Bound volume.
- Railway Express Agency, 1932-1936 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Express Messenger, 1932-1936 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.15 (1932/1933)-v.18 (1935/1936). Bound volume.
- Railway Express Agency, 1936-1939 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Express Messenger, 1936-1939 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.19 (1936/1937)-v.22 (1939). Bound volume.
- Railway Express Agency, 1940-1941 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Express Messenger, 1940-1941 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.23 (1940)-v.25 (1941). Volume numbering shifts from v.24:no.9 (1941:Sept.) to v.25:no.10 (1941:Oct.). Bound volume.
- General Electric, 1926-1929 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: General Electric News: Erie Works, 1926-1929 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    Author: General Electric
    Notes: v.10 (1926/1927)-v.12 (1929). Bound volume.
- General Electric, 1930-1931 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: General Electric News: Erie Works, 1930-1931 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.13 (1930)-v.14 (1931). Bound volume.
- Industrial Workers of the World, 1921-1922 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Industrial Pioneer, 1921-1922 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    Author: Industrial Workers of the World
    Notes: Series1,v.1 (1921/1922). "A Journal of Revolutionary Industrial Unionism." Greenwood Reprint (1968). Bound volume.
- Industrial Workers of the World, 1925-1926 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Industrial Pioneer, 1925-1926 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    Notes: Series2,v.3 (1925)-v.4 (1926). "A Journal of Revolutionary Industrial Unionism." Greenwood Reprint (1968). Bound volume.
- Standard Oil Company of California, 1924-1929 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Among Ourselves, 1924-1929 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    Author: Standard Oil Company of California
    Notes: v.4 (1924)-v.8 (1929)
- Standard Oil Company of California, 1929-1932 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Among Ourselves, 1929-1932 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.9 (1929)-v.12:no.7 (1932:Oct)
- International Labor Press of America, 1926-1927 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: American Labor World, 1926-1927 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    Author: International Labor Press of America
    Notes: v.27 (1926)-v.28 (1927)
- International Labor Press of America, 1928-1931 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: American Labor World, 1928-1931 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.29 (1928)-v.32 (1931)
- International Labor Press of America, 1931-1934 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: American Labor World, 1931-1934 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33 (1931)-v.39 (1934)
- International Labor Press of America, 1935-1937 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: American Labor World, 1935-1937 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.40 (1935)-v.44 (1937)
- International Labor Press of America, 1937-1940 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: American Labor World, 1937-1940 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.45 (1937)-v.49 (1940)
- International Labor Press of America, 1940-1950 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: American Labor World, 1940-1950 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.50 (1940)-v.68:no.2 (1950:Aug.)
- AT&T (American Telephone and Telegraph), 1950-1954 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Bell Telephone Magazine, 1950-1954 (Box 81, Folder 3)